[
    {
        "front": "Genkan",
        "back": "Entrance Hall",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Toire",
        "back": "Toilet",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Ofuro",
        "back": "Bathroom",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Senmenjo",
        "back": "Washroom",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Daidokoro",
        "back": "Kitchen",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Shokudō",
        "back": "Dining Hall",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Ima",
        "back": "Living Room",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Shinshitsu",
        "back": "Bedroom",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Rōka",
        "back": "Gallery",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Beranda",
        "back": "Balcony",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Okurimas",
        "back": "To send, to gift",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Owarimas",
        "back": "To finish",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Agemas",
        "back": "To give",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Moraimas",
        "back": "To receive",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Kashimas",
        "back": "To lend",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Karimas",
        "back": "To borrow",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Kaimas",
        "back": "To purchase",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Kakimas",
        "back": "To write",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Naraimas",
        "back": "To learn, to practice (by someone)",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Oshiemas",
        "back": "To teach",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Kuremas",
        "back": "to give (family or friend)",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Manabimas",
        "back": "To learn",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Te",
        "back": "Hand/s",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Hashi",
        "back": "Chopsticks",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Hasami",
        "back": "Scissors",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Kami",
        "back": "Paper",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Hana",
        "back": "Flowers",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Empitsu",
        "back": "Pencil",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Keshigomu",
        "back": "Eraser",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Shatsu",
        "back": "Shirt",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Purezento",
        "back": "Present, Gift",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Nimotsu",
        "back": "Luggage, Bag",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Okane",
        "back": "Money",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Kippu",
        "back": "Ticket (Bus, train)",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Korekara",
        "back": "From now on",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Ane",
        "back": "(My) Elder sister",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Onēsan",
        "back": "Someone else’s elder sister",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Ani",
        "back": "(My) Elder brother",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Oniisan",
        "back": "Someone else’s elder brother",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Otto",
        "back": "(My) Husband",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Goshujin",
        "back": "Someone else’s husband",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Tsuma",
        "back": "(My) Wife",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Okusan",
        "back": "Someone else’s wife",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Musume",
        "back": "(My) Daughter",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Musumesan",
        "back": "Someone else’s Daughter",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Musuko",
        "back": "(My) son",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Musukosan",
        "back": "Someone else’s son",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Gambarimas",
        "back": "I will do my best",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Subarashii",
        "back": "Wonderful, amazing, admirable",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Tokorode",
        "back": "By the way (while changing a topic)",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Hoshii",
        "back": "Want, Desire (for Noun)",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "~tai",
        "back": "Want, Desire (for Verb)",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Tenki",
        "back": "Weather, Climate",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Manga",
        "back": "Comic book",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Tokoro",
        "back": "Place",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Kakemas",
        "back": "to call",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Hagaki",
        "back": "Postcard",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "‘Dare ni’",
        "back": "‘to whom’",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Terebi",
        "back": "TV",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Rajio",
        "back": "Radio",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Repōto",
        "back": "Report",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Kādo",
        "back": "Card",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Kazoku",
        "back": "Family",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Mō",
        "back": "Already",
        "chapter": 10
    },
    {
        "front": "Mada",
        "back": "Still, Not yet",
        "chapter": 10
    }
]